{
    "id": "a011d8e0c85a41e6b661ddbabb381898",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Planets ……………………. round the sun.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "are going",
                "have gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "65b97221f8c74b60ac567c1e706d0225"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………. strangers.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense we make questions and negatives with do and does. Use does with singular subjects. ",
            "answers": [
                "has not trust",
                "does not trust",
                "do not trust"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4d75bc7b467b4e55a450aa9b8bfbe208"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………………… in the morning.",
            "description": "We use the simple past to say that something happened at a particular point of time in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "have left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6dc858e6ffbc4404b72e95a720833238"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… any rest since morning.",
            "description": "Haven't had means the same as haven't got. ",
            "answers": [
                "hadn't",
                "haven't had",
                "hadn't have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5d0475b6a3ed443a9a4193041a1f4e97"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………… from work yet.",
            "description": "The present perfect is more common with expressions like yet, already, ever, never etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "didn't return",
                "haven't returned",
                "hasn't returned"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f9a53f5edf57417896d36d5b9a2c84e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "May I know the reason why .................................... to quit?",
            "description": "There is no inversion in reported questions. ",
            "answers": [
                "you want",
                "do you want",
                "did you want"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "54ab0584da134e078bc8560efdec70b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can’t meet him now. He ………………….. to Australia.",
            "description": "He has gone to Australia means he is still in Australia at the moment to speaking. He has been to Australia means he has visited Australia at some point of time in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "has gone",
                "has been",
                "went"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "327f7d69ae784bd2aacc2012c6d6dc2f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you ever ……………………… to New Zealand?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "gone",
                "been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d8bfc26503ae4e179e7ce6331d2fe31e"
        },
        {
            "question": "This time next week, I ……………………….. in France.",
            "description": "Use the future continuous to say that an activity will be in progress at a particular point of time in future. ",
            "answers": [
                "will holiday",
                "am holidaying",
                "will be holidaying"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "858ae096562e4eaf996295658b5daaa0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The piper ……………………. the children to a river bank.",
            "description": "Led is the past tense of lead. ",
            "answers": [
                "leaded",
                "lead",
                "led"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "611cb5b2b4ea4be1840111d7d5c2a014"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. at 7 in the morning.",
            "description": "Use the past continuous to say that an activity was in progress at a particular point of time in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "jogged",
                "am jogging",
                "was jogging"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e6e50e2c198646c3b141aa4079368490"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. in Mumbai for 12 years when I got transferred to Chennai.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was working",
                "have been working",
                "had been working"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d10118fc1deb458e833412d2c782cf63"
        }
    ]
}